JARED WALKER

1726 Hampton Ct Farmington, UT 84025 • 801-618-7267 • jaredwalker.inbox@gmail.com • LinkedIn Profile

All models are wrong, but some are useful.

~ George Box

PROFILE

A social scientist with six years of experience with inferential statistics and data visualization. Has a working knowledge of research design, data collection, and hypothesis testing. Has experience delivering oral presentations and producing written reports. A person of character with reputable references.

EDUCATION

Master of Science Bachelor of Science		Political Science Political Science		n State University iversity of Utah	December 2022 August 2003
SOFTWARE APPLICATIONS					
Excel STATISTIC	PowerPoint CAL EXPERIE	r NCE	<u>Tableau</u>	STATA	Qualtrics SSMS
Data visualization	Multiple linear regression	ANOVA MANOV			- Outlier detection
Histogram analysis	Linear discrimi analysis		Markov cl		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY					

Data Specialist 801-538-7624 2019-Present

Utah State Board of Education - Salt Lake City, UT

- Participates in bimonthly townhall presentations to districts and charter schools.
- Responsible for internal and external data requests.
- Serves as Primary Point of Contact for reports such as the FNS-905 Summer Meals Report, Summer Meal Counts Comparison, SNP Claims Variance Report, CACFP Claims Variance Report, FRAC Afterschool Meals Survey, Federal Receipt Reductions Report, Count of Sponsors and Sites by Program, and the Food Safety Inspections
- Oversees data wrangling in the administration of P-EBT
- Serves as Second Set of Eyes for the October Survey and the CEP Annual Notification Report.
- Develops and maintains standard operating procedures on specified reports.
- Develops and administers internal and external surveys.
- Quarterly surveys include the CACFP Operational Waivers Survey, CACFP Administrative Waivers Survey, SFSP Operational Waivers Survey, SFSP Administrative Waivers Survey, and the SNP Waivers Survey.
- Achievements include statistical refinements to the claims variance reports, automation of reports in R, survey study on unpaid meal debt, Summer Pandemic EBT 2021, Pandemic EBT 2021, and Pandemic EBT 2020.

Technologist 801-243-2700 2007-Present

PSG Professional Services – Farmington, UT

- Duties include sleep diagnostics, generating physician reports, and management of patient records vis-à-vis the Easy III database.
- Prepares digital polysomnograms consisting of patient neurophysiological readings across multiple channels, including EEG, EOG, EMG, EKG, oxygen saturation, and respiratory flow.
- Scores sleep stage, REM, epics of wakefulness, and abnormal event data such as arousals, apneas, and involuntary limb movements.